const questions = [
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/Harry_Potter.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Flash",
        choice2 : "The lord of the Rings",
        choice3 : "Pokemon",
        choice4 : "Harry Potter",
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/The_Fast_and_the_Furious.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Need for Speed",
        choice2 : "The Fast and the Furious",
        choice3 : "Speed Racer",
        choice4 : "Turbo",
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/Venom.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Spiderman",
        choice2 : "Captain Marvel",
        choice3 : "Venom",
        choice4 : "Black Panther",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/The_lord_of_the_Rings.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "The lord of the Rings",
        choice2 : "Hobbit",
        choice3 : "Robin Hood",
        choice4 : "Last Knights",
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/Avengers.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Thor",
        choice2 : "Iron Man",
        choice3 : "Ant Man",
        choice4 : "Avengers",
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/James_Bond.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Get Smart",
        choice2 : "Matrix",
        choice3 : "James Bond",
        choice4 : "Wasp Network",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/The_Hobbit.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Captain Marvel",
        choice2 : "The hobbit",
        choice3 : "The lord of the Rings",
        choice4 : "Spectre",
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/Resident_Evil.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Resident Evil",
        choice2 : "Wrong Turn",
        choice3 : "The Deep House",
        choice4 : "The Night House",
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/Death_On_The_Nile.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Follow Me",
        choice2 : "The Little Things",
        choice3 : "Death On The Nile",
        choice4 : "Lost Girls",
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: `What movie is this from:<br><audio controls controlsList="nodownload noremoteplayback nofullscreen">
                    <source src="sounds/Forgotten_Christmas.mp3" type="audio/mpeg">
                    Your browser does not support the audio element.
                   </audio>`,
        choice1 : "Home Alone",
        choice2 : "Forgotten Christmas",
        choice3 : "Last Christmas",
        choice4 : "The Christmas Chronicles",
        answer: 2,
    }
]

export default questions